http://www.lucini.com/pages/california-privacy-rights

Try our award winning Premium Select - Shop Now
Shop Extra Virgin Olive OilOrganic Extra Virgin Olive OilInfused Extra Virgin Olive OilOrganic SaucesArtisan VinegarsAll Products Recipes ALL RECIPESBREAKFASTSTARTERSSALADSMAIN COURSESSIDESDESSERTS Blog Olive Oil TipsCooking Guides About Our StoryNews & Awards
Store Locator
Log in
Shopping Cart
0 items
Shipping & taxes calculated at checkout
Your cart is currently empty.
0 items
$0.00
Continue Shopping
Continue Shopping
0 items
Shipping & taxes calculated at checkout
Your cart is currently empty.
0 items
$0.00
Continue Shopping
Continue Shopping
Your cart is currently empty.
Shipping & taxes calculated at checkout
Continue Shopping
[[ formatted_image ]]
[[ product_title ]]
##OPTIONS##
[[ variant_title ]]
##OPTIONS##
[[ formatted_price ]]
##DISCOUNT_DESCRIPTION##
[[ discount_description ]]
##DISCOUNT_DESCRIPTION##
Quantity
##QUANTITIES##
[[ quantity_index ]]
##QUANTITIES##
Welcome!
It looks like you're located in:
Would you like to visit
instead?
Yes, take me there!
No, I'll stay here
BACK TO ALL PRODUCTS
STAY UP TO DATE
Join and get 10% OFF your first order.
Thanks for subscribing!
Thanks for subscribing!
No thanks, I don't want 10% off.
California Privacy Rights
California Privacy Rights
CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTSLast Updated: June 8, 2020PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY TO UNDERSTAND HOW WE TREAT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND WHAT CHOICES AND RIGHTS YOU HAVE IN THIS REGARD. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS POLICY, YOU SHOULD NOT ACCESS OR USE THE SITE OR ENGAGE IN COMMUNICATIONS WITH US CONCERNING OUR PRODUCTS OR SERVICES.THIS SITE IS INTENDED FOR USERS LOCATED IN THE UNITED STATES, AND IT IS NOT INTENDED FOR USERS LOCATED IN OTHER COUNTRIES, INCLUDING THE EUROPEAN UNION AND THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA. BY USING THIS SITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE USING THE SITE FROM WITHIN THE UNITED STATES.INTRODUCTIONThis California Privacy Rights page supplements our general Privacy Policy. You may obtain an accessible version of this Policy by contacting us via the methods identified in the “Contact Us” section at the end of this Supplement.CCPA NOTICE AT COLLECTIONFor purposes of the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”), in collecting the information described in our Privacy Policy, we collect the categories of personal information listed below. If your information is collected in the context of a business relationship with us, it may not be covered by the CCPA.CCPA CategoryDescriptionIdentifiersWhen collecting Contact Information, we receive your first and last names, email address, street address, city, state, zip code, and county.When collecting User Account Information, we receive your first and last names and email address.When collecting Financial and Payment Information, we receive your shipping and billing street address, city, state, and zip code.When collecting Cookies and Similar Technologies and Usage Information, we receive your Internet Protocol (IP) address or device identifier.Categories of personal information described in the California Customer Records statuteWhen collecting Contact Information, we receive your first and last names, street address, city, state, zip code, county, and telephone number.When collecting User Account Information, we receive your first and last names.When collecting Financial and Payment Information, we receive your shipping and billing street address, city, state, zip code, and telephone number; as well as your credit card number, security code, expiration date, other data to process payment.Commercial informationWhen collecting Order Information, we receive the list of items purchased.Internet or other electronic network activity informationWhen collecting Cookies and Similar Technologies, we receive the information described in the “Cookies and Similar Technologies” section of the Privacy Policy.When collecting Your Communications and Feedback, we will receive data related to if/when you open our message and if/when you click on any links or banners it contains, the date and time of your “click” on the email, a message number, the name of the list from which the message was sent, a tracking URL number, and a destination page.When collecting Usage Information, we automatically receive information from your browser and your device, which includes the date and time of your visit as well as your location, time zone, Internet Protocol (IP) address or unique device identifier, domain server, operating system, browser type, access time, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site and data about which pages you visit and how you interact with the Site.Geolocation dataWhen collecting Contact information, we receive your street address, city, state, zip code, and county.When collecting Financial and Payment Information, we receive your billing street address, city, state, and zip code.When collecting Cookies and Similar Technologies and Usage Information we receive your location while using the Site.Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar informationWhen collecting Communications, Feedback, Support, and Inquiries, we receive the subject matter of your message and any comments that you choose to provide.InferencesDerivation of information, data, assumptions, or conclusions from facts, evidence, or another source of information or data) drawn from any of the information identified above to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudesHow do we use these categories of personal information under the CCPA? We use the information described above in order to:Operate and improve our business and the Site;Provide you with the services, products, content, and functionality you request;Honor our terms of use and contracts;Manage our relationship with you;Process payments, orders, returns, and other transactions (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations);Improve our products and services and develop new products and services;Maintain our databases and back-ups, including records of our communications with you;Ensure the privacy and security of the Site and our services;Detect fraud and prevent loss;Improve our customer service;Communicate with you and respond to your feedback, requests, questions, or inquiries;Promote our products and services to you; Contact you about other products and services; Improve our marketing efforts, including by providing more tailored advertising;Administer a contest, promotion, or survey;Assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaignsSupport and improve the Site, including evaluations of functionality and features;Analyze use of the Site and our services and prepare aggregate traffic information;Recognize your device and remember your interactions;Provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on the Site;Determine and track user interests, trends, needs, and preferences;Facilitate corporate mergers, acquisitions, reorganizations, dissolutions, or other transfers;Obtain and maintain insurance coverage, manage risks, and obtain professional adviceAccomplish any other purpose related to and/or ancillary to any of the purposes and uses described in this Policy for which your information was provided to us;Accomplish another purpose described to you when you provide the information, for which you have consented, or for which we have a legal basis under law;Comply with federal, state, or local laws;Comply with a civil, criminal, or regulatory inquiry, investigation, subpoena, order, or summons by federal, state, or local authorities;Cooperate with law enforcement agencies;Exercise or defend legal rights or claims; andCreate, use, retain, or disclose de-identified or aggregated data.DATA PRACTICES DURING THE LAST 12 MONTHSPersonal Information Collected: As described in this Policy, we have collected the categories of personal information listed below during the preceding 12 months:IdentifiersCategories of personal information described in the California Customer Records statuteCommercial informationInternet or other electronic network activity informationGeolocation dataAudio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar informationCategories of Sources: We have collected the personal information identified in this Policy from you.Business and Commercial Purposes for Collecting: We have collected the categories of personal information listed above for the purposes listed in the “How do we use these categories of personal information under the CCPA?” section above.No Personal Information Sold: We have not sold categories of personal information during the preceding 12 months. Personal Information Disclosed for a Business Purpose: We have disclosed for a business purpose the categories of personal information listed below during the preceding 12 months:IdentifiersCategories of personal information described in California’s data breach notification lawCommercial informationInternet or other electronic network activity informationGeolocation dataAudio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar informationWe have disclosed each category of personal information to the following categories of third parties: (1) corporate parents, subsidiaries, and affiliates; (2) advisors (accountants, attorneys); (3) service providers (data analytics, data storage, mailing, communications, marketing, data transfer, website and platform administration, technical support); and (4) operating systems and platforms.NOTICE of FINANCIAL INCENTIVESummary and Material Terms. We provide special offers, discounts, and coupons via email throughout the year to individuals who are on our email distribution list or have an account with us.  By providing your email address to us, including by signing up for our newsletter, or by creating a user account, you join the many customers who receive promotional offers from us via email. The program is completely voluntary. Categories of Personal Information. This program involves the following categories of personal information under the CCPA: Identifiers, Categories of personal information described in the California Customer Records statute, and Commercial Information. How to Opt-In. You may opt-in to the program by signing up for our email distribution list or by creating a user account with us.   How to Opt-Out. You have the right to withdraw from this program at any time.  If you do not want to receive special offers from us via email anymore, you can click the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of our email communications or contact us at privacy@cal-olive.com. DO NOT SELL MY PERSONAL INFORMATIONUnder the CCPA, you have the right to direct us to stop selling your personal information to third parties and to refrain from doing so in the future. For purposes of the CCPA, we do not sell personal information as defined under applicable law.REQUESTS TO KNOW AND REQUESTS TO DELETEThe CCPA gives consumers the right to request that we (1) disclose what personal information we collect, use, disclose, and sell, and (2) delete certain personal information that we have collected or maintain. You may submit these requests to us as described below, and we honor these rights where they apply.However, by way of example, these rights do not apply where we collect or sell a consumer’s personal information if: (1) we collected that information while the consumer was outside of California, (2) no part of a sale of the consumer’s personal information occurred in California, and (3) no personal information collected while the consumer was in California is sold. In addition, de-identified information is not subject to these rights.If a request is submitted in a manner that is not one of the designated methods for submission, or if the request is deficient in some manner unrelated to our verification process, we will either (1) treat the request as if it had been submitted in accordance with the designated manner, or (2) provide you with specific directions on how to submit the request or remedy any deficiencies with the request, as applicable.Request to KnowYou have the right to request: (1) the specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you; (2) the categories of personal information we have collected about you; (3) the categories of sources from which the personal information is collected; (4) the categories of personal information about you that we have sold and the categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold; (5) the categories of personal information about you that we disclosed for a business purpose and the categories of third parties to whom the personal information was disclosed for a business purpose; (6) the business or commercial purpose for collecting, disclosing, or selling personal information; and (7) the categories of third parties with whom we share personal information. Our response will cover the 12-month period preceding our receipt of a verifiable request.Submission Instructions. You may submit a request to know via 1 (888) 558-2464 or by sending a written request to privacy@cal-olive.com or 1367 E Lassen Ave Suite A-1 Chico, CA 95973. If you maintain an account with us, we may require you to submit the request through that account.Verification Process. We are required by law to verify the identities of those who submit requests to know, and our verification process is described in detail below. We will inform you if we cannot verify your identity.If we cannot verify the identity of the person making a request for categories of personal information, we may deny the request. If the request is denied in whole or in part for this reason, we will provide a copy of, or direct you to, our privacy policy.If we cannot verify the identity of the person making the request for specific pieces of personal information, we are prohibited from disclosing any specific pieces of personal information to the requestor. However, if denied in whole or in part for this reason, we will evaluate the request as if it is seeking the disclosure of categories of personal information about the consumer.If there is no reasonable method by which we can verify the identity of the requestor to the degree of certainty required, we will state this in our response and explain why we have no reasonable method by which we can verify the identity of the requestor.Request to DeleteYou have a right to request the erasure/deletion of certain personal information collected or maintained by us. As described below, we will delete your personal information from our records and direct any service providers (as defined under applicable law) to delete your personal information from their records.Submission Instructions: You may submit a request to delete via 1 (888) 558-2464 or by sending a written request to privacy@cal-olive.com or 1367 E Lassen Ave Suite A-1 Chico, CA 95973. We may present you with the choice to delete select portions of your personal information, but a global option to delete all personal information will be offered and more prominently presented.Verification Process. We are required by law to verify the identities of those who submit requests to delete, and our verification process is described in detail below. We will inform you if we cannot verify your identity. If we cannot verify the identity of the person making a request to delete, we may deny the request. If there is no reasonable method by which we can verify the identity of the requestor to the degree of certainty required, we will state this in our response and explain why we have no reasonable method by which we can verify the identity of the requestor.Verification Procedures. To determine whether the individual making the request is the consumer about whom we have collected information, we will verify your identity by matching the identifying information provided by you in the request to the personal information that we already maintain about you. As a part of this process, you will be required to provide your email address. Authorized Agents. Authorized agents may submit requests via the methods identified in this Policy. If you use an authorized agent to submit a request to know or a request to delete, we may require you to: (1) provide the authorized agent with signed permission to do so; (2) verify your identity directly with us; and (3) directly confirm with us that you provided the authorized agent permission to submit the request. However, we will not require these actions if you have provided the authorized agent with power of attorney pursuant to the California Probate Code. We may deny a request from an agent that does not submit proof that they have been authorized by the consumer to act on their behalf.CCPA NON-DISCRIMINATIONYou have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment by us due to your exercise of the rights provided by the California Consumer Privacy Act. We do not offer financial incentives and price or service differences, and we do not discriminate against consumers for exercising their rights under the CCPA.CALIFORNIA SHINE THE LIGHTUnder California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use may be entitled to request and obtain from us once a calendar year information about the information we shared, if any, with other businesses for direct marketing uses. At present, we do not share your personal information with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the “Shine the Light” requirements and only information on covered sharing, if any, will be included in our response. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our Site may make any changes to their information at any time by contacting us at privacy@cal-olive.com.CONTACT USFor more information, or if you have any questions or concerns regarding this Policy, wish to exercise your rights, or wish to lodge a complaint with us, you may contact us using the information below, and we will do our best to assist you. Please note, if your communication is sensitive, you may wish to contact us by postal mail or telephone.In Writing: California Olive Ranch, Inc.Attn: Privacy Officer1367 E Lassen Ave Suite A-1 Chico, CA 95973By Email: privacy@cal-olive.comTelephone: 1 (888) 558-2464
TOP
